just me being schizophrenic in this
apartment : DOTA welcome back thank you
for subscribing
alright there really are people out
there it's great for a bunch of people
to get in here look I loaded the Python
notebook already I spelled Scala on my
computer to us playing with some
synthesis tools teach my friend came
over so I helped with their math
homework
yo what up Yas boss thank you for
hosting yo we are back boys we are back
I said fuck it I'm not streaming in 2020
and then well 2020 was this and you know
and yeah yeah so so we're back and we're
gonna do science today I think we're
gonna try gonna try to do science news
who's excited for for science 85 cake
thank you I'm loving all these
subscriptions I gotta get my income back
up you know guys I'm broke I lost a lot
of money I lost a lot of money
I didn't I didn't buy into the panic I
should have bought into the panic but
you know what they say
get an early garage getting like up then
I got thoughts so there's that yeah
everybody's all stupid but you know it's
really stupid i watch how many trillions
are they gonna print and hand out to
people
lots of trillions lots of trillions and
trillions out to everybody you get a
trillion you get a trillion
a large corporation of lobbyists I'm
sorry you don't get a trillion table
sorry
yeah well we needs to keep their doors
open guys we gotta save Boeing you know
oh we gotta save Boeing everything does
they pull out all the stops man no no we
don't we need to open source all Boeing
let everybody build the planes what do
you think how about a Tesla sentry mode
for crappy cars we redeemed sent a
message and sub only mode
what's sub only mode am I not a
subscriber to my own channel
I don't know Oh Eric HTP I don't know
what that is if you want to send the
link we're not gonna play any on here
cuz it sounds a little you know all
right we got a Tesla sensual what do you
think we do in this channel we do
nothing we shit talk while we click and
type quantum dota you're asking in the
wrong place you are a subscriber so I
will dig the file with the response oh
we're in sub only mode oh we in sub only
mode okay we don't have to be in sub
only mode welcome every ball that was
given us subs freedom on and even though
we were in sub only mode hello hello
what's up what's up yo I don't know wait
I'm gonna refresh this so I can actually
get a viewer account do I play video
games whoa yeah yeah yeah thank you
please subscribe to my channel you know
this is the only way
hutch twitch streamers or getting buying
these in these tough times yeah
we're gonna start with some paper should
I called it we're gonna cure the common
virus no no no no no we're not doing
data science we're not doing data
science don't worry no you don't have to
stay at home guys don't worry don't
worry don't worry they haven't deployed
the army yet you know when there's a guy
with an m16 in the street that's what
I'm gonna start to listen because I
don't have an m16 okay so I discovered
this cool website where you could
download the genome with a coronavirus
we can zoom in a little bit - yeah Jen
bag look at this
all right so we can get oh it's a sign
of an API look at this see this this
here is the coronavirus only or has a
the end of it is alright that's
efficient code the suit I'm saying right
so I want to do I want to do a few bits
of data science on the coronavirus damn
all right we got Corona all right how do
we do this I basically I only want the
a's t's c's and g's we could do it with
a filter we could do it with a darker
place okay corona equals corona the curl
is too long to type we're just gonna
call it CC we don't know what I'm
talking about
see see see see
I just want to get rid of all these
things sorry I'm not it's probably a
faster way to replace okay so welcome to
the corona virus genome this is from the
original sample in wuhan we might be
looking into learn the basic terms all
right so this is um what's the first one
how many base pairs is it let's just
google this number and see if I got that
right what happened to new Google this
number was a zip code base pairs oh yes
look at this everything the whole
Internet's about this stuff now so I
haven't taken a bio class in a long time
but we're gonna see what we can remember
so first off here's an interesting
question right
what's the cola magrav complexity of
coronavirus how many bytes of
information does it contain um can I use
XZ from the Python XC as much well Wells
you may I have I was in LA what I will
do this later Z live.com press
see no bites like object is required not
strange oh why do I use Python why don't
we go back to Python to no attribute
decode and oh yeah there we go okay so
how many this is remember you can only
upper bound column graph complexity you
can't lower bound column graph
complexity go to solo learner Kotick add
what's is biopython a thing let's teach
me so much whoa was any of this cool
it's like the API for biopython all
right so it's interesting that we can
upper bound the the the the coronavirus
at 8 kilobytes of information and I
suspect it's even smaller than that so
for a reference the smallest computer
virus I know about is sequel slammer
let's see if I can find the packet oh
wow sequel slammer oh this is this was I
this was an efficient virus it's only
three hundred and seventy three hundred
and seventy six bytes it probably
compresses even more 8k yeah how long
have I been program if I'm gonna zoom
out a little bit here so I can actually
see kind of like make the chat bigger I
can collapse the chat users and chat
nature yeah yo y'all we hack in nature
yo us we should name that we should
change the title we do coronavirus
science AKA hacking nature yeah cuz
that's what we're doing so you know
all right no I don't know let's uh let's
see if we can compress a little bit more
I'm sure the coronavirus isn't really
this large oh no I made my mouse really
sensitive
no it's still insanely sensitive oh I
could press down on this okay now is
less sensitive cool
do I have housing ma I have lzma and we
just put another cell here so I don't
keep running into that so I probably
shouldn't put the coronavirus on disk
all right
but by the way cost to synthesize base
pairs
just-just-just yeah yeah it's about ten
cents so remember that you know okay
yeah yeah so like that's well within the
range of a hobbyist you know now it just
was just exploring man or just exploring
we're gonna figure out like the strength
of its reading frames and stuff um DNA
synthesis service so like I wonder can
you can you like what if you upload this
to that
hmm no oh god you gotta go with the
expensive service if you want something
this long oh here we go
okay well you pay more if your price per
base pair is you guys do know you can do
this right I'm not like like spreading
like secret bioterrorist information am
i I'm just I'm just I'm just looking
we're just doing science we're just
doing science not it was one of the
things this is one of the things that
scares me you know it really wouldn't be
that hard
Oh
lzma makes it even smaller we get it
under 8k format XZ traffic's equals 9 or
one-shot compression and used-up does
this work this function take any
parameters so you see why I'm interested
in compressing right why do we want to
know what the compressed size is the
compress size so there's this thing
called Karma graph complexity
it's like it's it's a it's the short
length of the shortest computer program
that produces the object as output so
basically like how much information is
there in in the corona virus and it
turns out there's about eight point four
kilobytes the rumor is the corona is the
HIV sequences inserted into another
virus we can check that I don't think
that's true it's the same thing as
entropy yeah yeah pretty much I mean it
called our flux is measured in what is
the unit of entropy I guess it's the
same yeah I guess yeah it's really the
same yeah it's a number of bits but I
mean entropy the differences entropy
usually refers to randomness all right
all right all right I don't want to hear
any conspiracy theories about you know
China made it in a lab if that's true
we're gonna get to the bottom of it
right now as you know any good hacker
would definitely shut their handle in
here somewhere
so let's take a look and see if we can
find anybody's handle I show up in here
okay so I don't know what biopython is
but we're gonna just Google decoding DNA
into codons yeah so there's like a yeah
here we go this this this this this so
the pro Kang for those of you that don't
know well whether the basic bio here you
can decode DNA using this and these are
the different codons and they break down
into basically these I believe they're
amino acids is that right yes in
transcription the DNA sequence is
rewritten in RNA so there's no
transcription cuz this is a virus and
it's RNA don't okay if I
but any of this stuff yell at me y'all
probably know more bio than me but I
think the virus is RNA only so we're
just gonna do translation we're gonna
write some code to do translation so
we'll say like def translation now we
need to put in these codes a TCG what's
up with the use why are there use oh
it's a you because it's RNA I think but
that's a scam then why do they tell me
the the that this is a ste season geez
what's this is RNA though right I don't
know I think that's what the difference
is all right yeah dude the U is an RNA
yeah so but we I think we can just
replace it with the t's right so let's
make a dictionary uuu equals oh no okay
I don't know the amino I let's let's
look up amino acids right we'll learn in
here so I think there's like 20 of them
not 21 of the 21 amino acids there's
nine that humans can't synthesize and
then you can stick these all together
into proteins all right here we go wow
this is nice 21 amino acids
good they all have letters oh that's
that's convenient I've seen this before
and then we could we can check we can
check our results with diamonds who
plays with your cylinder I see someone
studied in bio wasn't me man all right
so we have all these letters we just
need to figure out which letters
correspond to which DNA sequences yo how
sick is it that you can decode nature
like this this isn't even that hard man
this isn't even that hard then ok so
then first we're gonna do the
translation and that way to get the
amino acids then we're gonna try to fold
the protein I took organic chemistry in
uh in college really just as I wanted to
learn to make drugs I'm not gonna lie I
wanted to learn to make drugs then you
don't learn that because they tell you
how to make drugs I mean they don't like
like do you get to play with anything
you know when you read like these like
recipes and like like you know Arrowwood
and stuff you want to know how to follow
them and I'm like I don't know then just
do a simple acid-base extraction what
the hell is an acid-base extraction
right you wanted to make aspirin in
first year or go wait Aspen's like
really complicated isn't it
oh no nevermind it's dead simple laughs
I didn't host them simple it was cocaine
is complicated you know look at all that
look at that making cocaine looks hard
my GPA was 2.78 in high school real talk
okay um can I just get this in something
I can copy and paste because I'm a
slacker yeah yeah yeah Oh perfect oh
yeah and now we're talking wait this
looks complicated here we go
oh look they even have the letters for
me in verse table for the genetic code
the DNA code on table compressed using I
you pack notation those are the fuckers
who did the org oh wow okay I don't
really care about what it is compressed
we don't need that we have args what is
a semicolon oh it was a fart bitch oh
[Music]
where is it compressed gay a yes n or
ASP /b yeah those are all raised
where's gal that's gap because okay fine
yeah well we'll deal with that we'll
deal with that this is still a whole lot
better than typing them all oh I see so
they just they synthesize it
okay
you don't need saw what is that
different I was like a tab or something
ggm don't care you a wide I don't care
kak thou start is OGG and stop is all
this stuff
okay cool okay let's just parse that
table out no just the table we'll call
this TT and I love naming my variables
right what is this is a tab tap teach
you got split tab is o X that's good
that's a first we'll say for T and T G
dot split new line you got split line
what told you to split based on new luck
Oh oops there we go okay this looks
pretty good
okay we're gonna separate this into kV
and we're gonna say if slash in a K got
split / so - one dots okay cool - many
values to unpack expected to above H
doesn't V have it - oh this kept a gun
in there yeah y'all ready done
good yeah gun control yeah
now the stick and hope we get more of
this no no no no guys guys there's no
plan yet you know if you're new in my
stream you think that we do stuff on
this strand if you're old to my stream
you know that we actually just shit talk
and do nothing all right
but while actually doing stuff it's
weird but it takes a bit to get used to
okay let's just say be equal to be dobry
cool ladies we're writing our own DNA
decoder you know yeah you ever written a
decoder for like x86 assembly it's like
that but for DNA man all right sweet so
these things decode to those days
now let's see do they usually just start
and stop a kind of stupid they not have
better names for these we'll look at the
translation yeah okay we're gonna figure
out where the proteins are we're gonna
break it all down can I get more
anti-state ramps nah we love this day
we're all good citizens of the
government right now and when they come
with the m16
all right I think actually before we do
that we're just gonna say dot lower dot
replace you with T because we're some
reason DNA okay cool
or V V and V dad equals that decks of V
V equals K okay now we have our stuffed
decode DNA with what did they can start
and stop letters you know the fridge is
empty but you check anyway no I was
thinking about ice cream but I realize
never need a lot ice cream today this
pickings are slim at the store you know
how we used to eat pasta that was a
luxury no longer affordable to us yeah
man how much of computers is just
parsing crap okay let's parse the
coronavirus for i in range one Wayne CC
three decks of CC so I plus three Kiera
AAA well we got to the end we made it
all the way
all right sweetie that means they all
decoded I don't know maybe they always
all decode I will just call this a a
because it's an amino acid chain AAA
append Dec all right okay
well so now you're gonna get into stuff
called reading frames now there's
actually three reading frames does
everyone know that so reading frame who
knows why cuz it's three right who gets
it yeah yeah you get it right cool let's
go so this is all the proteins that the
virus can possibly Express let's just
throw up
join AAA in there and let's see if we
did the decoding right okay so now when
I look for the translation of this it's
not in my shit and I probably did it
wrong these are mess there's no mess no
net glue oh there's no app I don't know
Sarah it's an S I don't know we decoded
all turned reading frames met/met is the
start codon no it's not no no let's try
just like one of these sequences let's
see if I can find it hmm you guys what
if we uncover some crazy shit right now
what if we uncover that they're lying to
us about the translation net is the
start codon oh man is the start codon oh
shit you're right you're right all you
go yo yo
your bro your bro yo okay we you telling
me there's a you a a somewhere here
where's the stop codon something else as
well so that's such a scam because met
is both here ended start oh we didn't
think about that
oh if V V in Dec print do V V
oh there's duplicate song wait no this
sucks
if I have an AAU how do I know if I'm
getting an as in or an ASP me just sucks
man why would they do this
this is the shittiest encoding I've ever
seen
nature is troll gay alright wait wait
whoa wait this is just stupid they have
as in and then they have ass and then
why do they have as in or ass oh I don't
know whatever this one can go Glen or
glue can go why would they do this they
have Glenn glue and then Glenn or glue
well never using that one the start
codon is stupid too because it's just a
mat now oh yeah oh yeah decoding let's
see if there are any more dupes why okay
there's actually lots of tubes right now
but that's just cause no okay cool let's
see this is quality is quality science
boys it's quality science
all right let's go Jared you're new
around here
there's no point man you know all right
oh stop oh that's just cuz I put a stop
that way could the stop be called
something else let's see if they call it
something else here well you know what I
can just do a a dot split on stop
oh yeah well there's a lot of stops it
probably prevents stupid crap from being
copied damn nature's smart man look at
these big-ass proteins I'm finding okay
oh yeah yeah I mean okay I don't know I
got a mess in here somewhere
TPA RVL all right all right f ln RV hmm
it's so close
we're so close look I found this see
gasp RVP okay
let's replace stop with dollar sign what
do y'all think of that oh look man join
I don't know what that means
five prime UTR oh this is pretty cool
let's do okay God replace stop with a
dollar sign now that looks too much like
s what else can we use redial that's a
good one
yeah redial sorry about you counseling
people I call it redial all right let's
go let's go let's go what is this
okay equals Kate our place yeah man
would try to find the exploit you think
there's an x-point who thinks there's an
exploit sort these by lengths
Rittenhouse we don't talk about comedy I
in this stream this is not oh yeah good
look look look my shit decoded the same
as their shit almost there's bugs in
line let's figure out where those bugs
are EQ LK do we have this one we have
this line do we have this line we have
this line do we have this one
we have this line oh we probably have
all the lines we probably just don't
have cool all right look we found this
big chunk of DNA what is it it's a
ribosomal slippage it's an or flap poly
protein interesting leader protein or
flaw poly protein hey do we have this
one
oh it's part of this one too
ah okay okay I see I see I see we should
also probably split on ms well wait so
you're telling me all this shit is
really just one Northington
filter lambda x you know it's like you
ever use strings this is just like you
some strings but you set the end to 220
you know it's only fine big proteins oh
go we got proteins we got proteins um
spike glycoprotein produced who figured
all this shit out man
it's pretty brilliant you know these
people the og reverse engineers man
they were reverse engineering before
computers whatever all the letters wants
in language so biology is kind of like a
like a CAD program alright so and DNA is
like it's on disk storage format and
then it goes through this process called
its transcription what's the central
it's called the central dogma of
molecular bio or something yeah here we
go
describes the two-step process
transcription and translation but I'm
pretty sure I'm gonna get news I hate
news news is disgusting guys don't read
news
it's RNA right here we go
as a positive sense single-stranded RNA
virus was positive sense meaning may be
directly translated into viral proteins
[Music]
yeah central dogma a DNA and RNA go
backwards cancer proteins back in the
RNA but you get some of that reverse
transcriptase man I want to eat
something but all the good foods they
eat a long time about here everything's
like sweet disgusting I bought some more
vegetables
[Music]
we got our lives does this this is we
even here in quarantine
yeah man manufacturing consent yeah I
know my Chomsky's hmm you can figure out
this RNA sequence of a protein though
right well I don't know actually don't
know if you can all right so these are
the proteins
do I have this one membrane-like over
team
oh yeah look at that we got that whole
protein there
we love lime the lime is delicious okay
structural protein membrane like Oh
protein now it's time to do some reading
Oh
negative sense oh I understand it's a
file cat okay so it works in like the
normal reading frame well that's cool
yeah Dana this girl she knew everything
about biology
where's positive sense sense or polarity
yo now you know what we could do
alright so now that we have all of these
weight is met the start is met oh I
think yeah like Mets the amino acid that
like doesn't attach to the others or
something yeah so these are the these
are the amino acids in nature we could
figure out how to stick them together
and then try to fold both but yeah this
is kind of where you get you know this
is one of the problems with bio it's
like this isn't code why is this the
first one after because of the sulfate
you know what there's probably a whole
Wikipedia page on methionine
it's like Hermits you know it's like
Hermione
Hermione meth my knee are the only salt
foot protein or genic oh they're used to
make proteins are all of them protein oh
genic how many do we have that's a
question we can just ask by saying om
deck
oh no wait 64 oh that means that every
single one of these decodes now that's
actually not the question I want to ask
I want to ask lend set deck values 21
and that includes stop so I'm interested
they said there were 21 amino acids 1 2
3 4 5 6 7 8 9 10 11 12 13 14 15 16 17 18
19 20 21
oh no there's tryptophan which one of
these is not here then which which amino
acids not used in a protein ah the 20 of
the standard code plus Celeste is just
shy lean oh we don't have any shalash to
shush Eileen all Celino proteins wow you
can really they really aimed everything
something here there's like a whole
world of stuff I just don't know
that's decoding everything in every
reading frame protein oh we have that
whole protein the or flaw poly protein
by Google this is it tell me something
cool that's a good product while buying
worth of poly protein oh here we go
wait look look at that Dow it's it's
from SARS cough it's not from SARS cough
- is it it uses the same protein nature
reused code
hmm interesting
nature knows about stackoverflow Real
Talk oh look we can see it oh yeah
pretty cool man nice 3d model all right
we have an or flow poly protein on our
mat peptides so I think bio is like it
also like uses different reading frames
okay that's the or flab poly protein I
don't know why this like dot is there
cuz it's like a join but it seems
alright well let's just see if like
their numbers match mine let's just
write a function called death decode
take an X so that should actually be
minus 2 there
[Music]
when X was 2 X and now we can say you
know well decode the three reading
frames variety code reading frame 1 0
you know x86 code is reading frames -
all right so let's see if we get the
same results as these boys no don't tell
me they're little fuckers and they start
with one no
- one doesn't make sense
oh no it doesn't make sense because they
stopped Lua fuckers there probably what
inclusives as well
are they inclusive 'z wait what I don't
want T's when I get teased
there's weird break because that now
matches
why are we getting all them stop codons
I was just trying to decode the one gene
you know oh I say that's weird why are
they both or flawed polypro oh this is
an or flab product is an or flaw poly
protein this is an or flab - I don't
know bio doesn't make sense name these
things like computer people and things
that makes sense oh look at that oh we
got a stop codon right there you got a
start codon alright this seems like the
main protein this is an off or a flawed
polypro to you and this is the protein
ID oh that's nice Oh
see this one comes from Sarris - but
SARS one has an oracle poly protein -
[Music]
now the truth is man you want to talk
about how calm a I skirts regulations we
don't talk about common AI but like we
kind of don't like Cobb a I actually
operates completely within the law you
don't even piss people off you know we
talk to regulators it's like pretty fine
on the whole comic probably's and that
safety benefit by see the car companies
make money by selling cars ma'am if you
disrupt biology there's a whole scam
like like like you know how I say
self-driving cars are a scam like those
companies at least like you know are
trying the medical companies
people who buy our research this genius
is doing this but like you know with
insulin in America's $600 someone scam
and mad someone stabbing to Rio heart
let me explain to you how you know if
something's a scam it was one of my
favorite graphs
consumer prices over time however I've
ever done this um now there's the one I
really like ah this one yes yes so
basically here's the quickest way to
tell how much of a scam something is you
look at this chart
alright 1998 everyone remembers 1998
right like that wasn't that long ago
back here you know what's really not a
scam televisions televisions now
[Laughter]
televisions everyone knows is not a scam
because you can spend like I bought my
TV was - what was $150 it's like 42
inches it has built in Roku TV it's sick
look where the scams are hospital
services I mean like they correspond
with what you know is a scam right like
you know or health insurance all we need
universal health care no no regardless
of whether we need universal health care
why the fuck does it cost two hundred
and thirty percent more for hospital
services now than 1998 it hasn't even
gotten better medical care hasn't even
gotten better in the last twenty years
but you know what has gotten better
televisions and toys and software man
when people make jokes about oh yes
offer gets where software gets worse
until you try to use some software from
1998 you're like holy shit this is
terrible
wireless telephone services I got like
like I got like five G everywhere man
and I paying nothing for it it's
SiC alright and then you get to like
close furniture and cars they've gotten
better too even though it's zero they've
gotten better because remember there's
inflation right like furniture man you
wanna seem sickbeds off of amazon but
nothing close have gotten great all the
high-end brands make street where cars
have gotten way better do you think
modern cars break they just don't like
like if you buy like a 2020 toyota
corolla that car is never gonna break
all right and they get to the things
that are like okay housing people
complain a little bit about housing okay
food and beverage there's no one
complains that much you know it's that's
alright it's alright because you know
earnings outstrip those and now you get
into the two things that everyone in
america complains about and maybe this
is just an america problem they're like
health insurance is so expensive and
college is so expensive we need the
government to pay for them no you need
the people who make televisions to start
making college shit man if samsung made
college that shit would get bigger and
thinner and better and cheaper every
year but no it's made by scarce and you
can just tell you can just tell let's
see who's the president of harvard right
right yeah you want my auntie government
is my auntie government look at this
fucking guy right like I don't even know
who he is but like you know he's not
like you know look at him look at him
now let's look at the president of
Samsung right look at this guy man who's
the scammer right you just tell you
could just instantly tap look at this
guy he's holding up some sick-ass flat
phones and this guy sticks his logo
everywhere and puts his hand in the air
like he's preaching you know
just knew was gonna come out that way
man look at this you see that guy man
fully that guy ran harbour and I bet you
Harvard would be awesome but no no he
doesn't run Harvard this fucking guy
runs all right so like you know you talk
about comma and you're talking about
disrupting these people like they're
really not scamming like the recent
Toyota sucks at making like cruise
control and lane keep assist system is
just cuz of how they're structured it's
not because they're scamming you right
like those cars aren't really worth
their money I would recommend a new
Corolla or a new Civic to anybody you
know and people can even complain all GM
and Ford they're not bad they're not
great but they're not bad right
then nothing like these people alright
that's that rant and you know I spread
it to your friends the last thing we
need is free health care and free
college because all that is people you
know I don't understand are the same
people complain about income inequality
and then demand free college and free
health care you're just giving more of
your money to these folks you know
notice the man did Universal TV we need
universal televisions
yeah because televisions were up here
people would
[Music]
Oh freedoms all right so this is the
protein we have now yeah and fast n GN
fat perfect there's also an or flaw poly
protein for the other wanna others
there's cool ways they do like distance
as you know
to give them all these names and stuff
you just will have a wipey
oh here we go look it's almost the same
faster oh yeah perfect
I got a name it's our second actually
might even looking at the right protein
is the or flip ollie protein important I
mean it looks big so you would assume
that where they put lots of code it's
important you know the answer close
it's the Edit distance look I'm not
talking about whether health care is is
you know what I don't know I'm not a
politician man health insurance by big
TVs is there not a scam don't ever ask
why who asks something oh no no yeah we
don't talk about the keyboard no no we
don't with my we're like oh no did I put
my window somewhere my window went away
did I close it you guys probably saw
what happen to my window would it go
well open we know again the window is
back where let's make sure you still
have stars v1 oh good we have stars
anyone okay good okay how close is SARS
v22 SARS v1
first off let's actually okay
they're almost the same language I
really does reduce so we still have
that's about without half the code is
for the or flaw poly protein there's
also a spike glycoprotein genes synonym
I should probably stick with worth one a
be aa function catalytic activity but
don't isn't that like the Krebs cycle do
I think I'll get the virus if you ask me
to predict fifty-fifty I'd bet against
it I know people are saying everyone's
gonna get it
there's also a spike glycoprotein and it
seems to be that yeah cool not just that
what else do we have that has code in it
and there's a little bit of code in the
nucleo capsid protein not much you don't
like little bits of junk
this thing's mad simple
it's folding at home try to fold these
it's a virus it's tiny just two caps it
and some RNA I see I don't know what a
CAPTCHA this this this is this is
protein shell of a virus all right so it
has a caps it doesn't seem to have a
capsid which one of these is the capsid
protein casing that has the RNA it I
mean there's only a good 3d model of
this thing so just pictures then I know
it it it binds to a stew I've seen these
before tell
so what's on your X chromosome that's
cool
that might mean that might explain why
women wait is this coronavirus
entry-point thing is this I go back in
history
hmm okay interesting this thing is just
famous for being a part of coronavirus
epic geo Tennyson - Wow
that's it it's just that many of you
know how that oh I could build this and
sell this sounds Pleasant you come from
2030 you have vaccine can you post I
will synthesize think about it we'll
just go - we'll go we'll think about if
I could just write - right like 8k of
code but I'd have to write literally
eight kilobytes I could make a corona
virus that has no symptoms but is
incredibly violent and triggers the same
immunity I mean it's effectively a
vaccine but see that's see see that's
the kind of vaccine you know you could
make a vaccine that just spreads right
free shit for everybody I saw that in
season 4 episode 4 of reboot but the
problem is this codes really hard to
write like if deceptively small and
simple but like protein folding still an
unsolved problem deep mines been making
some progress with it but like you just
don't know you just don't know how much
computes really needed to do this all
right well look this or flab trolly
protein thing has to be important
because unlike you know unlike in code
where people write hundreds of megabytes
to include sparkle framework to do
updates it takes you know if they could
make a smaller virus it would just you
know can make more copies of itself more
cheaply so codes expensive for viruses
so this thing's got to be really
important I'm still I'm still stuck on
this thing it's half the code
what's a peptide oh yeah no well then
like okay amino acids become peptides
tetrapeptide oh yeah okay this is a 5
end and the 3 end you I cannot remember
this
don't you have to have ten years of
testing before we ship I mean yes that's
that's kind of that's kind of yeah
that's what they say
amino acid peptide protein are that
makes sense that means a chain oh okay
it's straight enough protein that makes
sense I like Matt peptide so yeah cool
they're breaking it down into peptides
right this is really like you can you
know just like function is like well so
you have you have like you know you have
like your bites then you have your
assembly code with bytes or like your
your DNA's your your assembly code is
like your your these thingies your
peptides will like your basic blocks
your protein to like your functions so
cool man
so cool
is that like a good bio gift I want to
dip I really want to dip coronavirus
with SARS I know we can see this is also
like strong and weak codons read about
this because there are like multiple
codons that code for each some of these
like do better
biopython oh is there something voice
sequence oh look at this someone's
already written some code for me
nucleotide is transcription and back
transcription it just changes the TZ to
use translate using nucleotide methods
to stop
this biopython thing doesn't look very
together because the next step is really
hard right like if you want it if you
want to decode this more like great
alright okay there's a spike like
approaching like it's small but going
from that into something is pretty
difficult let's see
protein structure prediction
scam
this is tiny 820 bytes it's kind of a
lot like I guess this thing sounds like
a function right Oh taps its we learned
about cap since the or do rf9 notes a
another term for a Meerut human herpes
virus three
this protein clearly is not important
because nobody named it anything
structural protein a protein nucleo
capsid phospho protein so I'm gonna
write like a good medium article on this
SARS comp to jeans breakdown here we go
yeah Wow Isola is a nice picture
what's an amino acids well that's
beautiful
does this match the number we're seeing
I got the length of that let's print
that again so sorry too should have a
length of 44 or 5 ok 44 six because
they'll get rid of the stop um we can
say just dots giraffe
if it does end with a stop codon just
well you know what we can do just know
you know what it's not called decode we
should use the real name central dogma
biopython named it the right thing
Moll bio it's called transcription
translation
Wow this is quality code man this is
quality code yeah so we write tests who
wants to write tests all right so we're
worried we're on the cob Wikipedia page
it's the thing if you search for
coronavirus you get shipped if you
search for Sora's cob - you've got
things that are slightly better who's
everyone chat is not paying attention
stream I'm on chat now all right so we
also spend a lot of money on this or
f---one a so lean to the spike
glycoprotein that's s I don't know why
it's different
did I use the same I might not have
started with the same thing in GenBank
did I seems right the reference sequence
is identical okay I don't know why my
ass is too wrong but okay they spent a
lot of code on this or f1a as well
oh that's worth one a and B is the IC
yeah or for a poly protein but where's
our f1b
okay this okay I see this has a
different reading frame or one B equals
translate we're also going to say a
search a sub 0 equals M should be fine
we'll say protein all right it's a whole
protein it has a start and an end that
makes that track
okay let's see if we can decode this or
f1b okay I think it's just a different
reading frame
hmm weird weird
five FLN see that's not right
where is this well that's just the or
flip Holly protein but hmm
okay seems okay oh look look look look
look this number is different from this
number yeah does he look this overlap
look at that see what what what hacking
skill you know
they overlap the code a little bit
oh look at that that's really cute
I'm look they use a star we should use a
star that same is better why are they
getting multiple Emmys they're getting
ttg zaandam CTG and ATG and I just got
ATG where is you Yugi they're getting
you Yugi as a as a loo hmm ours don't
have these problems right
oh man look at this there's different
texts on those different processors
which do the separate things a little
bit you know not wait so we got to get
down to the root of what this other poly
protein someone was someone was telling
me what this protein does there was
something somewhere that liked to had
like a description I'm not sure if I
believe it but yes let's go back to that
picture I like that picture I don't want
on Wikipedia this is like a nice visual
layout of the code I mean we really need
Kiera for bio you know where's Kira at
oh you can build some sick tools for
this
thank you laughing though it didn't come
from bat soup I think it did come from
bats but I think there was a there was
an animal in between I don't know I
don't think we know yet okay it
catalyzes ATP plus water into ATP why
does that body fall for this shit you
know this is human coronaviruses HKU one
is this the other human coronavirus it
must be it's the wrong protein
yeah and I want a date with this other
girl she explained to me of like you
know the krebs cycle she's like yeah how
do you not know ATP no no I don't know
what is this ATP to ADP isn't this like
the body's fuel source I don't know what
it does with all that phosphate
catalyzes this reaction okay virus is
sure spending a lot of its code doing
this so this must be really important to
it and then this we have this spike
glycoprotein and we have a bunch of like
tiny little functions yeah this is
really like this really looks like a
computer program you know you have like
big function other function maybe M is
like main you know I really like this
picture
the spike is the key all right all right
the spike glycoprotein you saw me this
is the key this is how like it attaches
to the ACE inhibitors or something
it is just SARS Cobb one also use uh
[Music]
just does it also use ATP or does it use
ace the primary human receptor of the
virus is this so this is the thing the
viruses are scamming it's a single pass
type one membrane proton
I heard of these but if a lot of old
people are on them
you're ace inhibitors of high blood
pressure
there's also our what's our
never saw never donated stolen laptop
they was Wi-Fi all right this code
both of them just catalyze a reaction
and then viruses trick your body into
replicating it doesn't your body
replicate DNA like how do viruses
replicate
can be directly translated into protein
in the host cell that's fine but how
does it replicate
and I know they hijack your bodily
systems oh no it doesn't have I know
through this thing about been applying
the replication code I know that's
hijacking viruses you know they're
clever
they're called it all the subroutines
all over my body you know right why
would I want to write the replication if
I could just make a function call
coronavirus spikes consists of two
connected halves spike activates yeah
well yeah yeah yeah DNA RNA protein yes
I understand I understand that my body
that it uses the RNA to protein from my
body but why is my body replicating RNA
be translated into protein in the host
cell if it how do you get more of it
like I know there's reverse
transcriptase this is well like we block
to block HIV why doesn't this block all
viruses
watch this guy's video on coronaviruses
this scientific or is this some like
you're gonna die yet no I don't care if
it's what you should do
unless what detail does it go into okay
okay all right so we have a jointer only
inspecting this membrane all right
watching party 2019 the Chinese
authorities notified the world the
difference was spreading through that
community
okay don't care it's pretty don't care
about the news don't care this virus is
the severe acute respiratory syndrome
related coronavirus to the causes the
disease called coded 19 and that
everyone simply calls coronavirus what
actually happens when it affects is
human and what should we all do
[Music]
use Allan Jannis Caballeros is really
just a hull around genetic material and
a few proteins lipid envelope RNA spike
protein oh damn look at that code reuse
look at that code reuse the Spike
glycoproteins being stuck everywhere you
see this that shit turns into that yo
that's crazy
its main way of spreading seems to be
dropped infection wait viruses don't
survive they might no longer survive the
intestines I am just really curious
sorry about the ATV what is trending
right now
the most boring things you can believe
what
you
yo I'll believe in my thousand dollar
check when I get a thousand dollar check
right now
I ain't seen shit Indiana sent a guy to
give me that check and is he gonna come
with an m16
that's my only question if it's a guy
with an m16 they can keep the check
these are just a few coronaviruses can
cause quite a traumatic situation
running your organs and you cosa waiting
to be infected
Korona connects to a specific receptor
on its victims membranes to inject its
genetic material the cell ignorant of
what's happening execute the new
instructions which are pretty simple
copy and reassemble we're okay okay okay
where are those instructions where the
direct deposit they gonna put that shit
my bank account the original virus until
it reaches a critical point that
receives one final order self-destruct
the cells sort of melts away releasing
new corona particles ready to attack the
more cells the number of infected cells
grows exponentially after about 10 days
millions of body cells aren't wait can
we just talk for a second how there's
more copies of this code out there then
like
infected she'll know I found that with
do my taxes based on you your an immune
system the immune system while there to
protect you compassionately pretty
dangerous to yourself and needs tight
regulation and as immune cells pour into
the lungs to fight the virus Corona
infects some of them and creates
confusion cells have neither ears the
rice they communicate mostly fired tiny
information proteins called cytokines
nearly every important immune reaction
is controlled by the corona Cordish it's
like a huge game as crazy many murder in
a sense it puts the immune system into a
fighting frenzy and sends way more
soldiers than it should wasting its
resources and causing damage to kinds of
cells in particular recover first
neutral files which are great at killing
stuff including ourselves as they
arrived in their thousands they start
popping out enzymes that destroy as many
friends as enemies the other important
type of cells that go into a frenzy of
killer T cells which usually order
infected cells to commit controlled
suicide confused as they are they start
ordering healthy cells to kill
themselves to the more and more immune
cells arrive the more damage they do and
the more healthy lung tissue they kill
this might get so bad that it can cause
permanent irreversible damage that leads
to knife locked into the guy in most
cases all care systems early ricans
it kills the affected cells yes all
across the state trying to affect new
ones coming on the battlefield recovery
begins the majority of people infected
by Corona will get through with
relatively mild symptoms but many cases
become severe or even critical we don't
know the percentage because not all
cases have been identified but it's safe
to say that there is a lot more than
with the flu in more severe cases
millions of epithelial cells have died
and with them the lungs protective
lining is gone that means that the
alveoli tiny air sacs file which
breathing occur okay I know this part
the part that I don't know cells have
murder is until it reaches a critter I
did what's happening execute the new
instructions which are pretty simple
copy and reassemble how does it yeah
execute sir all its victims membranes to
inject it there's genetic material okay
the shirt sure so you got this exploit
you got you got a stew it's vulnerable
um this shit shows off this spike shows
off which is basically just like the
exploit vector exploit vector comes in
and jacks its payload all right it's all
the same shit it's really all the same
shit you guys you know your study
computer security you know this but now
execute the instructions whatever I
hijack AIP I jump to the viruses off all
grey copy and reassemble it fills up but
where is that where is the copy function
you know also yo I don't know how any of
this shit can work
search structure of virus okay and then
it uses reverse transcriptase why the
hell do I have reverse transcriptase
I mean is it using this so I don't have
HIV I don't have leukemia and I don't
have this daltin
so why do I have any reverse
transcriptase there were little machines
in your cells that only make copies of
RNA what the cells already have a copy
function oh no the cells have a copy
function for dear
not for ribosomes
this one says ribosomes I've heard this
before no no no ribosomes did you
translation that's fine
there are cells constantly reading the
DNA to make proteins okay RNA dependent
RNA polymerase is this it oh okay okay
is this what it's using
you know I believe a lot more in the
information about SARS than I do about
this new shit meth-head Mike I think you
might have got coronavirus replication
Oh even better
ah okay infection begins on the virus
spread glycoprotein all right so we
decoded the glycoprotein attaches to its
complementary host cell receptor which
is a stew after attachment of protease
of the host cell Cleaves and activates
the receptor attach spike protein okay
so there we go
you know let's put it into computer
terms so the glycoprotein does a heap
overflow and overflows the next segment
of malok after the next thing has been
overflowed a free from the host program
cleaves and activates the misaligned
pointer alright it's like a use after
free and it frees it I that's great very
on the host cell protein available
cleavage endocytosis
when entry to the host cell the virus
particle is uncoated the exploit payload
is unpacked and its genome enters the
instruction cache and it's instructive
and its code enters the instruction
cache the corona virus RNA genome has a
push EW at the beginning of the function
and a pop a IP at the end of the
function which allows the virus to run
without disrupting anything else okay
the sequences written in
x86 which allows it to yeah translates
the initial overlapping open reading
frame and forms a long poly protein
that's this shit this is the poly
protein right yeah your flaw worthless
the poly protti I don't know what a poly
protein is that means it's got to two
shits yeah that's two it has the 1a and
1b all right cool
has its own protease is which cleave the
poly protein into multiple non
structural what no but what that's not
what it said did it said it did
something stupid is this thing lying to
me
okay the poly protein is very important
this is the unpacker for the thingy
maybe
yeah well share vaccines of subs if I
find a vaccine I'll share it with the
subs that's right so you better
subscribe like it's just so the same you
know just okay not one of the non
structural proteins coalesce to form of
all of the wah ah the non structural
proteins coalesce replicase yes
meth-head Mike was right dork mode thank
you for this link we finally got some
real information it's not like a youtube
video I heard a good joke there was a
conference the Dutch conference of the
world exploit the world experts in
coronaviruses but it was postponed
because of the corona virus pandemic
alright we should read this okay ass
protein okay we got the S protein
quantifiers is bind on the cell
[Music]
and it can produce in the cytoplasm
first a virus and the size its RNA
polymerase
no let's read about this so I assume I
have this polymers
wait why
so wait a second do I have this protein
when I'm focusing on anything you
misunderstand and we're asking questions
do I have this protein oh my god no
that's what this shit is that's exactly
what this or flah prolly protein is is
the copy mechanism hi I don't know I
guess I just assumed that no it is
look accepted named RNA transcripted RNA
polymerase it does the same thing
nucleotides triphosphate ATP is
adenosine triphosphate phosphate
catalyzes RNA template directed whoa yo
that's sick man this or flow Polly
protein is the copy mechanism copy spike
and then reassemble with the little
shitty Co okay won't make sense all
right so it looks like this virus is
spending weii I mean it makes a lot of
sense that this virus is spending
two-thirds of its code copying this is
yeah yeah this is this is basically a
minimum like RNA copy Ritchie because I
knew your body didn't have RNA copy
routines the spike glycoprotein this is
this is the this is the exploit this is
the payload and the payload basically
just says make a copy and these are a
few helper functions I look at this
stuff and I have a framework right like
I have a framework I have a framework
with which to think about all this right
like you know you write computer viruses
you know how to do this all these people
I don't even think they had those
frameworks like and then the question is
I mean I I come into this world really
really late scientist you're all science
is all built on the shoulders of giants
and stuff so like I wonder if no but I
think it's fundamental like I think it's
fairly fundamental to how a virus would
operate because computer viruses have
very similar stuff
all right they have an initial they have
an exploit and then they have a payload
and you know this if you want payloads
that are just gonna like you know
rapidly copy themselves most viruses
have this some viruses have more
complicated payloads to do more things
how do we put a mining payload up to the
virus we can farm crypto I agree we're
gonna make corona virus pay us back you
know you know that's what we're gonna do
that's gonna be the gold as stream you
know we lost all this money and it was
thanks to this shit like this this code
this code cost us you know that many
bajillions of dollars
[Music]
no but if I eat all the chicken tenders
now there won't be any chicken tenders
later but I want them so we're going to
do it ooh chicken tenders that's a
pathetic amount of chicken tenders
and then we're out of chicken tenders
tomorrow we're gonna have to go braid
the store already ate a pizza today
[Music]
eventually we're going to get into
eating flour can you eat flour all right
maybe it's time for a little coffee kind
of dumpy doesn't feel strong enough
we're gonna wear this off biology is all
about
now let's get some clean socks socks
socks ha ha put on these socks
I mean chicken tenders whose
speedrunners Dave flower
[Music]
all night
oh yeah coronavirus hack speedrun nah
man it's the first time I'm playing the
game alright so what do we have to do I
[Laughter]
mean you know what's crazy right yeah
any for sanity present you know it's
crazy like you could take this you can
modify it and you can go like set it to
a lab and have it synthesized for like
you know 10 grand so I mean yeah we can
like that's so I mean yeah the code is
all nice and safe when it's in my
computer here but not so easy why is it
not so easy
DNA printing RNA printing service well
okay base pair let's see what we can get
printed this is all hypothetical don't
actually do any of this guys I'm not
actually gonna do it don't worry
oh my god
3d printers for DNA this is horrifying
laser based technique wait what
have this guy died
whatever they don't tell you I usually
think it's suicide yeah
sad use a laser-based technique to
synthesize DNA Wow your biggest we just
gotta make the right mods we gotta hit
print wait
okay like for everybody who thinks cava
AI is scary
holy shit that's scary
it probably doesn't work but you can
okay there's definitely like DNA
synthesis service no one finds County as
scary no once you actually see what it
is it's okay cargo drive to LA right now
people a lot of people don't know it
alike you know that you need a person in
the driver's seat is actually a lot of
that person's actually in the driver's
seat
well we're not working on backspace
right now backspace is hard math is hard
move you my discounted price okay so if
I buy them hypothetically if I buy some
DNA oh oh
free conan optimization you say a very
interesting optimized that's janked
degree
okay so I understand that when I get my
printed DNA it's not gonna be assembled
into a little coronavirus I'm not
actually releasing a vaccine guys don't
worry I'm just I'm just I'm just this
hypothetical okay don't ever don't just
just you know I'm not a doctor I'm not a
doctor don't don't rely on me for
medical advice or anything important or
if you if you're taking my advice and
you're changing the way you live your
life you're probably an idiot why can't
I just use something like CRISPR Wow
let's see no I don't have any DNA here
not none of this is DNA I mean okay so I
think what I would have to do like how
do I then inject my DNA into something I
can make RNA into DNA yeah well okay so
let's say I got it let's say I got a
corona virus synthesized in DNA right
then I mean I need to put that DNA in
something that would do transcription to
turn it into RNA and then translation to
turn that RNA into proteins and then
again it'd be in the wrong place right
Wow but I mean once you do it once right
you only have to do this once in a lab
and then you get it right and it
replicates forever DNA dwelling and
plasmid vectors
things plasmids are a cloning vector
small piece of DNA I say
should I know what a plasmid is no that
wasn't that other thing that I was
looking at right I didn't know the name
of them it's not a peptide a genetic
structure that can replicate independent
of chromosomes okay I understand so it's
like a combi so well I have a lot of
tabs open look up a YouTube video on
plasmid vector that we're back to video
watching time it's learning bio
what what I have to pay an extra hundred
and oh my god they're already scamming
me we verified deposited plasmids do you
have a good video cleaving enzyme if I
need it what am I doing with a cleaving
enzyme do I need one of these
Furyk wait whoa whoa wait I think
coronavirus was using these I think I
heard about this Joe needs to make an
extensor which removes unnecessary yeah
yeah the hard part is figuring out which
ones are unnecessary little Dirk is
definitely unnecessary sorry a little
dark
what is crisp right now we don't need
crisper we definitely don't need cocaine
[Music]
we're done with protein structure
prediction
just have a human long do the
transcription I mean yeah so the problem
you can have a human long do the
transcription if what you know but like
like I'm not gonna get it in in
coronavirus form right I get it in I get
it in I don't even like know I guess
they give it to you in terms of a plasma
am I gonna regret this mute rx what
should I listen to you know I know about
PCR
though this seems worth watching will
start after later what do we got here
[Music]
cells containing plasmids and clothing
is amended by isolating a particular
sequence of DNA from a complex mixture
of different DNA sequences in a host
cell
generally a plasmid vector contains four
elements a cloning site this is a swab
be inserted a drug-resistant gene which
displays antibiotics in this case
ampicillin to allow selective growth of
the host cell and a replication origin
to allow the plasmid to replicate in the
host cell to insert foreign DNA we must
first use of a fiction enzyme to cleave
the vector of the cloning site here eco
r1 Cleaves the palindromic sequence
g-a-a-t-t-c
to produce single-stranded ends called
sticky ends these can hybridize with any
piece of DNA that is also in Kakariko r1
for a DNA containing the sequence we
wish to clone is digested with eco r1
and then mixed with the cleaved vector
the sticking ends of the foreign and
plasmid DNA molecules hybridize and then
are sealed into one spot diaster
linkages by the enzyme DNA ligase
creating a recombinant plasmid hmmm all
right so I got a lot of plasmids that
sounds biased each of these recombinant
plasmids contains the inserted DNA
fragment and ampicillin your BIOS really
open source DNA doesn't need a checksum
because it has so much redundancy in it
each plasmid carries an unique fragment
of foreign DNA as indicated by the
colored arrows next the host cells equal
my bacteria are added to the recombinant
plasmids the cells have been treated
with calcium chloride to make them
permeable to DNA molecules through a
process called transformation a few
cells take up a recombinant plasmid
while most other cells do not and then I
put the antibiotics in and I kill all
the other cells that sounds nice the
e.coli is replicate see this is what
biology sucks man
[Music]
biology sucks
meu direct school with ampicillin and
younger yeah yeah and that was good for
shadowing when they put that in the in
the plasma it's good for shadowing now
seven degrees multiply because they
cannot move on the auger each will
produce a separate colony of cells all
right okay okay okay I'm with you so far
now I've got to get this into lung cells
I got to get this DNA replicating inside
long
plasmid replication is independent of
host cell division but plasmids are
distributed to each daughter cell when
the host cell divides as the plasmids
replicate and the host cells multiply
the number of copies of the recombinant
plasmid is greatly amplified the
multiple daughter cells form a colony or
close because all the host cells that
colony are derived from a single cell
they don't contain 22 but in time it
wouldn't it yeah but again all right
great
I have lots of copies of my DNA I got my
bacterial copying my DNA that's great
but like well huh actually wouldn't the
bacteria Express the proteins
yeah viral is different from bacteria
but no I'm saying that you make that DNA
right so I mean the bacteria like e-coli
is gonna have all the transcriptase
stuff
why not long cells are eukaryotic okay
yeah I know viruses can infect bacteria
exactly so basically I'm you know I'm
giving the coli coronavirus right oh god
okay okay should I still you're right
all right they're different I should
have studied that right I should have
studied I'm sorry I slacked off and
infile
that the prokaryote ecoli is a
prokaryote not a eukaryote rodeo
bacteria oh you have a Gram stain yeah I
heard about this once
yeah okay I can see how that works
you carry out
yeah okay so it's got to have a nucleus
and it's attaching to a Stu on the lung
cells
I heard of sous-vide what's that my
cooking
Wow Wow
that looks like a nice steak man it's
been a while since I've had a steak you
know Oh salmon that sounds delicious but
this is a point which is a pointer to
just want me to look at pictures of food
the prokaryotes and eukaryotes are all
or all shit to deal with later but I
think we have the basics understood it
injects with this thing let's see if we
can understand what some of these other
guys are doing some of these other
Orff's well I guess maybe what is it
Worf stand for me is it all part of the
fucking pangolins man it's these guys
that's what gave us coronavirus thank
you for subscribing please subscribe to
my channel if you appreciate this kind
of content I'm going to see how many
subscribers we get if we get a lot of
subscribers I'm gonna keep doing this
we're gonna do more coronavirus science
tomorrow we're gonna make some real
progress yo just imagine just imagine I
just imagine you guys here when we solve
it man you know it's like when you're
being in the channel and someone does
the speedrun the speedruns are sick yeah
yeah you know I'll send you guys the STL
file for the vaccine yeah and I know
about this
she look they have like tools from like
like dot matrix printer are yeah let me
get out my Epson thank you for
subscribing no no no we're not done
speed run on life no but no no we're not
getting distracted anymore we're gonna
look a little bit into whether we can
understand these ORFs we're gonna eat
some chicken tenders and then that's
gonna be the end of this stream let's go
back to here we go is this yeah
can we understand what these other
Orff's are structural protein membrane
glycoprotein oh here we go
envelope protein membrane glycoprotein
there's more Orff's there's a lot of
stand for something Oh open reading
frame well that's what you're trying to
tell me oh okay well that's stupid why
don't they give it a useful name that's
just calling it fungus shit you guys
know it either when they just call it's
like function one function and then the
address that's so stupid
no no but it can't that can't be what or
if means because how come when I google
this unless this is just the most famous
or
why don't they name it something better
why don't they name it our DRP or
something why do they name it or they
can't possibly just mean open reading
frame that's so dumb or if one a be poly
protein that basically just doesn't say
anything surface glycoprotein what I'm
to spike a minor difference
surface glycoprotein why did I call it I
called it spike didn't I yeah that's a
spike glycoprotein are they calling it
surface
no I don't think it was a designer virus
right because it was a designer virus
like unless you're also alight well okay
so you're saying someone took SARS and
modified it like if you want to go with
that theory at the Wuhan Institute of
biology
Wow
it's our level 5
biohazard extraterrestrial materials
and that's a pretty odd coincidence
all right we're gonna dive into a
conspiracy theory for one minute here
Oh
and where's the coronavirus Wuhan market
well they're in a different district
let's see how far Dingaan is away from
Jing Shia
Wow pretty far
okay all right
five blocks away that's conspiracy
theory seems like how much 10 is doing
fries
no it's not suspicious people think a
woman has a one as an institute of
hydrology it has this market once the
city of 11 million people I dated a girl
from move on yeah exactly
every time a big stick has a research
center no it would just be suspicious if
they were around the block is all
no no that's I'm not saying it's a good
spirit but you're clipping an accident
but doesn't seem like it I mean I guess
like how would you tell no I'm not
saying I'm no one said purpose it could
have been an accidental escaped from a
lab right all right a mistake but no I'm
Joe
kind of virus state by accident yet sure
but none of that none of that seems
plausible nah but even like enough I
mean it is odd that it's yeah biosafety
level 4 but like I don't know that much
about the first SARS outbreak
Sibbett it's always like some bullshit
animal you know
I'm not reading the news on on
conspiracy theories
well so they say what changed is the
spike Mike leaving the spike is what I
read so that spike like a routine is is
different and let's get the SARS
no I want
ah here you go look it's like the
Wikipedia page but for og SARS you're
really very similar well see wenzels
I'm gonna get that in here no I like
this but fur genome assembly like holy
shit this is just SARS I don't know
maybe it all looks very similar
there's so many subtypes
there's a cleaner guy structure than
Khurana
there's a whole lot of flus
oh my god this one when there was
scaring us about the swine flu but this
is too beautiful edible shit no no no
they did the death rates lower they have
to make trade-offs you know engineering
is all about trade-offs the flus work
like this
it's just there's just so many of these
yes
what's us
and you know what a while them do hitch
a ride
yep this thing looks nothing like the
flow
well HIV is a whole nother thing right
yeah no HIV is caught hey check these
long right
Corona bars with some money HIV
machinery no way HIV is a retrovirus
it's turning itself into DNA the law of
equivalent exchange that's right
pollution is just SARS guys coronavirus
is too nice of a name
Oh
well now we understand why the Chinese
reacted the way today now it's always an
open question right like why do the
Chinese go into polling saying lockdown
because it's arks
well let's okay let's take a look at how
different um GHB that isn't true the flu
kills a whole lot of people but wait I
don't know where this myth came from
this thing is just not afloat it's just
SARS let me get all right let's take a
look I mean it's almost identical to
this let me just turn this into a
function
let's see how much mutual information
they have you can get like an edit
distance
[Music]
well no pneumonia is not anything there
is what do you mean unnhhh ammonia right
my understanding is that pneumonia is
just so they're literally they added a
little bit more code to the corona virus
it's not a flu I don't know I mean I
hear X it just seems like a journals
journalist met damn if they just called
it's ours I would have sold all my stops
they called it a flu and the only thing
I remember was the 2009 swine flu which
everybody freaked out about that turned
out to be so stupid cuz it killed nobody
man like what was the death rate from
swine flu like they they freaked out
endlessly about swine flu and the death
rate
oh my god no news yeah a lot of people
got it but the death rate was yeah see
this is the whole thing yeah the death
rate from swine flu was point zero two
percent no what
yeah but it's only because sorry's
didn't spread they actually managed to
contain SARS well until now
oh yeah this works
okay so the Edit distance is that
there's like nice
I don't know I think about the news is
the news as idiots like the metal block
right like there's a thing as soon as
you learn like you and then you read
like an article about politics you're
like wow this journalist is really
intelligent but the truth is they're all
idiots like the journalists have no idea
at all what they're talking about and
that's why you know you shouldn't read
the news it's it's just it's literally
just yeah yeah Gelman Amiga is that it
um there's okay all right I'm sorry I
shouldn't really hate on all on all
journalism period journalism is
uncovered some great things usually well
informed org is a bit better sometimes
they just write good stories too right
like there's definitely value in like
right like a ten page story like you
know III signed up for corporate
Corrections as a prison guard and here's
what I discovered it's like okay that's
kind of interesting right so I'm not
talking about that as news I'm talking
about anything if it ever says breaking
news it's a scam
well let's just call it SARS b2 I mean
this just seems great
I've seen naked and afraid I mean look
you you have to know that it's an ad for
naked and afraid but like wait was it
galvanized Eva yeah
[Laughter]
[Music]
all right I think it's bedtime if y'all
want to come back tomorrow I think we're
gonna do some more coronavirus science
tomorrow and we're gonna be a little
more strict on the yup yup yup no no no
guys guys guys guys guys
no we're gonna be more strict on the
moderating the chat I'll give a shit
when you call it this stupid with 3d
printing tomorrow or maybe maybe you
think we're gonna solve it you think
we're gonna crack it
you don't Rex yeah you can be a mod
Congrats only shit I don't know mute or
x-linked good stuff and that's why he
gets to be a mod 550 people time to stop
streaming yeah I don't know guys look
I'm not trying to subscribe and I'm more
like the extreme high will you do you
want to do Q&A now what Q&A do you want
what Q&A will do will do three minutes
of Q&A what's my schedule I don't have a
streaming schedule because the second
you have a scheduled streaming owns you
and your own streaming did you figure
anything out today yeah there's so much
shit man I learned that the corona virus
is just SARS how much of my stock prices
drop only cuz you're a subscriber I mean
like you know I lost love can you
explain the Gelman amnesia effect Google
and it basically journalists of morons
yeah yeah I discovered how great that's
true opinion of Martin shkreli you know
people always ask me
I think that we should hang out and
smoke some weed and listen to the Carter
five the oil thing I don't know it's
some vague thing between OPEC and Russia
you're trying to learn coding I don't
know man
do a pro like you can't like like like
imagine you came on here and said I'm
trying to learn Spanish what should I do
I don't know go to fucking Spain or
Argentina or something and just talk to
people you want to code like you know go
somewhere people are arriving that
shouldn't say it's don't talk to people
just code go somewhere with this code
and talk to code AWS is giving 20
million for Carano research can I get
money I'm doing corona research oh I got
to make an organization nevermind this -
whatever someone said D is for December
- actually what a simulation yeah yeah
probably you sage maker what's sage
maker this is this some bio shit or we
only do buy on you a new buyer oh this
looks stupid you guys hiring a comma a
yes if you want a job a comma right this
is the one time we're gonna shell for it
go to comment I and click we're hiring
we have a whole list of jobs for you
guys do I think that I could beat you
with Smash Bros Smash Bros 64 I'll bet
100 bucks that I beat you when will this
be over fucking no man ask a journalist
don't lie to you that was great if
you're not a software engineer can you
got a job at comment no he's money
everything that matters in this life no
money everything that matters in this
life no you gotta get money and fuck
bitches it's both of those things what
the hell is a computer engineer learn to
code we have a new we have a new
programming challenge now if you get
past our phone screen I did the
programming challenge I did I did the
programming challenge today so I'm
hacker it-it's a lot of fun is the green
matter I don't care if you have it the
green man
if you pass our challenge and managed to
get through talking to me by twenty
minutes and not say anything stupid
you good what's a data engineer can you
code bro you like the alternative cows
and I kill them that's good yeah a lot
of people got hired based on the speed
programming challenge that's good good
books on finding exploits from books man
just go find exploits yes open pod no
we're not okay with knives I were done
talking about comics yeah of course it's
open path development still happening I
don't know let's go take a look it's all
open source now oh I say let's say a
thing oh well okay I guess I mean no one
did anything today cuz it's Saturday but
like did people do commits yesterday oh
yeah look at all those commits yeah wow
it's a lot of kinetic so cool right what
do you think about Facebook AR you mean
oculus all right I know all the good
people laugh about that go at auger and
ask them that why not use Twitter my
Twitter socks it's the news social media
fit figured out how to turn you make you
as stupid as a journalist econ a real
field to enter no what is it
how's the notch I've been chewing way
less ice
I've been reducing my ice chewing social
medias are real virus to be eliminated
that's right let's mutate coronavirus
take out social media well I don't have
a quant funds cuz
care about money opinion of physics
physics is cool I like physics what are
my thoughts on MBAs it's is MBA and MLM
is that like you get MBAs and then you
convince other people to get MBAs and
then you know journalists are stupid
just smoke weed day four of quarantine
how real is the dunning-kruger effect
which ones that again my social
distancing well now that I know it's
SARS maybe I should start yeah and see
oh yeah yeah I know this one I mean like
I know I'm an idiot man speaks Luna
comes to this there's some things I'm
good at like about like hacking and I
was good at hacking five years ago
now I'm actually legitimately good
itself for having cars if you're one of
those things about self-driving cars I
know a lot about self-driving cars if
you want to know speak about by how I
don't know shit yo I can't talk to you
about ps3 se FW is no actually there's
no more court system did I go to college
I've been to a college yeah tire thing
gonna lie Abed read about the one of
ours for them to read kind of quietly
you don't have any skill set on the
common guy we are hiring page and why
the hell would I hire you no we're not
hiring for both developers one's even
gonna buy it we're not selling it Elon
do any nootropics know do you have the
coronavirus no how long did you go to
college I'm not been there about a few
times how do we hack the simulation well
we can't even figure out at a hack
coronavirus I think the simulation is
gonna have to wait what's my favorite
fantasy series I don't know I thought
Lord of the Rings sucked
I enjoyed Eragon the oldest
read those both the fact of the dare
exteriors goods liner one cameras better
the lidar do you hire interns yes
computer science major is sure but you
gotta know how to code about a few times
how many cups of coffee I don't know why
were you employed at Facebook
I don't know do things I worked on a
secret project no remote no what's my
favorite sex position missionary is the
classic for a reason
do I like porn huh yeah I like foreign
hub yeah can you program the cure for
crew no we're gonna try come back
tomorrow we're not learning how to do
what I do right in front of you few
texts are mutex oh man I know about that
few text exploits well I can't read any
faster I can't read all this where is
Alex I'm not here anymore
not here he's gone what do I do in the
time being I don't know inoculation is
probably the smartest route yeah maybe
do you accept computers I don't know
wonderful side boob and for the
questions I what's under boob what
happened to my sailor honour they got
this new hoodie Alex guy for me actually
miss Alex how many people work in your
comma three thousand you just do things
don't ever mention mayonnaise in here
again it's disgusting
p2p vs. cloud p2p all the way bro do you
centralized 20/20
yeah but washing my hands better hey
only it's a little shit man hey Olli is
just the Damali of mayo you know I don't
understand you know when I say things
like that who gets that like who gets
that when I say a Olli is the Molly of
Mayo currently hiring interns yes we'll
hire interns you must be very good if
you're asking me that question a
question but maybe you're very good and
then give me a job at comm a BAM Utah
Rex
wait who did you turn out a subscriber
Mueller X you can't timeout the
subscribers you have to be nice to the
subscribers alright the mods are running
wild are they is me or axis shitty majd
we get rid of him
should we on the mod mute our X let him
stay
alright alright let him stay all right
we like a minor that we like of money
school too much power for one man mod me
instead I don't know you who else wants
mine
wherever meth-head mic is who linked to
the RNA transcriptase thing he could be
a mod what's slow room mod the entire
chat who are you people meth headlight
congratulations your mod I trust you we
don't ask about the keyboards yeah yeah
you'll stop for monitor you guys can
solving them maybe I'll make you model
think about it what's a good coder man
yo you got a link if you if you
contribute positively to the chat you
can't be a mod
[Music]
No being good at hacker range is
definitely not overrated
what do you get if you contribute
negatively a band band add five cases
subscriber it's calming I unicorn who
said if I say well worth a billion
dollars will be worth a billion dollars
I can't type that fast you're done with
the elitism in leaders everywhere that's
right that's right Bernie Sanders lost
and it's a terrible tragedy it's a
terrible tragedy and he should stand up
and fight it's comedy I a pony scheme
[Laughter]
rip Bernie I know I know ever done with
imposter syndrome that sounds like
something bitches get have you opened
your third eye yo Alex got me this book
about color meditation and I've been
trying to do it yeah it's really hard so
ladies have backs me it's not really
been working on backspace it's been a
hold whose house you I don't know like
some company built it I pay them a bit
of money and live here sous-vide yeah we
learned about that this dream yeah
[Music]
well together
Alex and I are still friends yeah we
cooked today we cooked we cook some
chicken chicken fingers no I'm not
married let you get mine no challenge no
tiger you'll probably beat me I can't
type that fast
should we live streaming IQ test I don't
know vacuous do you have an addiction to
learning man you'll get modified no give
mine if you contribute positively to the
channel and ask me for mod is not
contributing positively to the channel
Ok Go has AK Ovid forecast challenge
yeah I saw that but it looks stupid it
looked like like I mean what is it like
I don't I don't really know how how is
it evaluated
huh
predict basically the countries I say
there's a coronavirus
Oh
hmm
it's cool I have to look at them more
about how this works maybe we'll look
into it tomorrow
what tool is this
startup looks a little scammy but well
let's look a little more before we
before you say that
equip your business for AI independence
yeah it seems scamming
where is this in FDA trials
hmm
we're next - what is this YouTube video
[Music]
wait Britt next - do you recommend the
wait just some fear-mongering shit it's
actually pretty cool
[Music]
nice and fear-mongering shit there's
kind of sick beat up huh
but it's interesting it's a relatively
small molecule viral RNA polymerase wait
so it's RNA dependent RNA polymerase
these links are all and evades
proofreading yeah yeah this is smart
because there's no reason there's no
reason bodies humans don't do this
humans don't don't replicate RNA from an
RNA template delayed chain termination
instead of buying 1080p it binds to this
shit
time iris
all synthesis is right here come on
there buddy fentanyl from China
can I buy this how old us people buying
fentanyl from China and I can't buy
resume to here
[Laughter]
look can calm it's just like like yeah
where can i buy like research chemicals
and stuff is there any place I could
just like paste in uh mmm seems like a
scam
what
never heard of cybersyn this seems so
stupid oh no wonder no no I'm not
looking I mean I should be able to look
can I get this thing synthesized
[Music]
delicious you drink a Bud Light i'ma
watch some television
Aaron Traywick dumb fucking research
chemicals
waitwhat
no this guy's an idiot and od'd on
ketamine
what's it what's the ketamine you know
you know what I'm saying though like
effective dose to lethal dose
I don't know
I'm on the list now for googling why no
I don't think you got murdered I think
you took ketamine passed out a float pod
and drowned
I don't know the guy but I know people
like that I think he's an idiot
I think the real tragedy is the other
guy yeah the guy who killed himself no I
know
look I know people personally who've
used CRISPR like who Chris Pope
themselves like you can do it now I
don't have any Corona no Corona here Oh
custom synthesis yeah but I'm sure if I
go to sigma-aldrich they're gonna be
like that's patented it's a smile string
just like computer that's pretty cool so
you don't have to learn all that that I
you pack naming conventions anymore
I mean NEVER said there's some cool
people in this space the IO pack over
smiles who smiles in some weird yeah no
I don't know I mean like people with
dyed hair and piercings I take less
seriously if he's here that color was
crisper all right that's cool
crispin themselves you know modify their
DNA with CRISPR I'm just saying if I
have some room suit aveer no I guess
people who are gonna die or like you
know
huh
Charles had my first ablative safety
profile monoclonal antibodies these are
the new like scam super expensive things
this is just some chemical it's easy to
make I mean I'm sure that's easy for
exactly someone could probably do that
like you know it's like cournot grad
student could probably do it who med
chem Express received of you can I buy
it
whoa
huh all right let's look up the dosing
research chemicals man which is phase
three I should know this 200 milligrams
ah this looks expensive
[Laughter]
what else can you buy on med on med chem
Express oh my god these people are
capitalizing on it
[Laughter]
Wow
I love capitalism and I wish not it I
wish it was all unregulated you know
people would figure out mad fast this is
all unregulated people who figure out
mad fast what works and I've seen this
I've seen this and I question it ya know
I read this paper last night no war on
drugs there's no regulation yeah you can
buy you can buy some crazy ship in you
go to our research chemicals yeah I got
stocks and I'm upset that I do I should
have sold them all about the go like
that congressman
what's Nancy Pig smiles database and
support and info well you need to
administer by IV if every junkie on the
street can do that you know shot
yourself up with something now chat over
half can't be that hard you think that
med chem expresses affront no I don't
think so let's see what these people are
gonna call them
a statement on false report
Selleck chemicals is trying to defame
meg have expressed
these people get cited this has to be
pretty legit can I buy it from them
we're SIM to here's new oh oh
I hope taxi chloroquine I don't know
let's see what it is and how it's
supposed to work what does it do
interesting I mean it doesn't seem like
it's targeting the virus yeah check
Trump's Twitter yeah that's the place
where I don't know is this the kind of
medical is this medical advice that
Adreno Chrome is the real drug
yeah I've seen adrenochrome was like
isn't isn't this unlike what I've seen
this like you would just inject
adrenochrome and then you become like
Wolverine
oh no it was fear loathing
yeah it seems like it make sure you
insist so exactly like their target is
targeting a very different thing it's
not targeting the virus I'm just I mean
I'm not am i serious effective you said
this does not really bite
cool
this is all you know none of them none
of this things we're actually gonna do
guys it's just interesting you know but
you could you know they're all
treatments I mean the difference so this
looks like it helps you if it's
progressed a bit but this yeah hmm
well now looks like news nucleotide
analog
top you're gonna check some things of
life mRNA vaccines
you know this synthesis is actually on
the website they don't know what the PD
page
I'm this guy in high school was great at
this stuff
yeah a co2 is I don't even know what AC
is AC uh an element it's not an element
does it so fuck it's an element has
anyone ever heard of this thing before I
usually need to get some actinium is it
radioactive is that I don't think that's
what AC means there
welcome to 6989 to close yes this is if
I want to make an arc reactor do I need
some actinium oh that's a city can
hydride and that's what a co2 Wow yeah
see there we go waffle ninja 100 waffle
ninja 100 knows what's up this looks
like something you can buy DSM Oh what
dimethyl salt the god side something
i've seen that that should som like
wiper fluid if you had cybersyn yes is
this something you linked to before that
I looked at briefly and some like
Chilean socialist shit alright
Chilean socialist shit band you're a
biochemist to Stanford I'm cool
waffle into 100 congratulations you're
also a mod provide useful information
you get to be a mom yeah I heard
Stanford's not giving any money back and
they canceled the foot classes hey you
know learning chemistry
I know three minutes is over well we
just started learning you know once you
start learning you can't stop we learned
about ascitic anhydride we learned about
some places you could buy verse in de
vere but it's very very expensive you
can't stop playing Wow Wow you know I
remember that 15 years ago I had a level
60 I'm gonna still be count on eBay and
I made money and it was like sick it
was-- go going what's Azariah I mean
like what's the WoW story now is it
still the Alliance and the Horde reddit
for research how do you find researchers
and investors oh yeah you can make cash
selling those things brought Pearce's
wow gold Empire I said I started
coronavirus Technion both tech
communities check that see what we got
that's catchy
then a lot of people are gonna try to
monetize the shit out of this you making
your employees work for mo collective
workplace
I didn't board up the door what are we
thinking about the next-gen consoles I
know like nothing about them let's see
what they are PS 5 vs Xbox whatever Xbox
X let's take a look Wow ok well I mean
it's pretty obvious which one's better
they really went all-in on AMD get
fucked Nvidia that's what you get for
postponing ampere
what sick
this is big navvy I know AMD people are
hyped on big navvy
oh yeah it's our DNA - okay so they're
both they're both gonna have big navvy
cards well that's crazy
now that you see the car that we really
want is Nvidia amp here and they just
postponed it due to coronavirus well
also because Nvidia sucks and they're
like oh we already hope the top video
card so why should we release the new
one good
it's stat eeeh oh it's many by Google
yeah I know it's not profitable to
release it and this is that okay all
right now now we need to bring the
socialism mean a planned economy for
gpus we need to plan to comedy for
Moore's law we're going to socialize GPU
products so we can make sure that we
continue to get new GPUs do I think the
money printing is right I don't know
okay look I really actually don't think
it matters at all basically here's the
scam they print money and they give it a
rich people but rich people already have
all the money anyway so like yeah it's
all the same
he's getting video make good Linux
drivers why don't they open source the
drivers your Facebook ethics question
have you ever heard my opinion on ethics
it's not very high whatever people talk
about ethics it's usually just a way to
control other people if money printing
is a thing why do we need taxation
because you know why else would the
money be worth anything right the only
reason the money's worth anything is
because taxes need to be paid in the
money and if you don't have enough for
the money to pay the taxes they show up
with the m-16 ethics exists because
people have feelings Commons policy of
the trolley problem is we disengage
that's a human dilemma their overnight
loans yeah I hope the loans and they're
probably scam people and yeah but you
know Boeing needs to fit out yeah Boeing
doesn't need to fail what needs to
happen is like just this need to DTaP
the whole organization everybody who's
like you have engineers and then you
have managers and then everybody above
that at Boeing is fired
Oh yo when's GTA 6 coming out
yeah we don't know anything about it
really yes and stock buybacks should be
illegal our stock buybacks legal what's
cyberpunk 2077 this is a game I don't
fall games that much
I don't know
wait is it gonna require a 1080 TI oh no
this is what they ran the DEF CON it'll
be the game of the decade maybe whoa it
uses an engine that's not unreal like
unity
what's gonna come out on stereo I get
job I miss dementia just uh you know
when you go home at night and you tell
your kids do not play the record player
so loudly and you got to make sure that
when you're dealing with domestic
violence you just got a punch it man you
got to punch the violence yeah it's my
favorite game of all time Super Smash
Brothers 64 yeah man
yang was our one true hope you know he
was gonna give me free money I love free
money but now we couldn't have the free
money that they had to say no to free
money check Twitter fuck Twitter check
Twitter gangs coming back weeks because
they're gonna get their act together and
they're gonna pick gang gathered yo yang
Gabbard now that'd be the ticket
Calle I don't know man I don't like
Kanye's new album that much but I did
hear goodness infections by anybody but
since to Hillary Clinton anymore is
money actually useful to you or you do
this for fun I mean everyone appreciates
more money look I bought myself an
iPhone 11 Promax with your subs money
can you upload an apple at the corona
code yeah yeah I don't know where I'll
upload it tomorrow if it becomes good
hack everyone sees from is anybody
allowed to participate you meant to
apply what's my computer's back that
you take any supplements no coffee my
interested in being a guest probably not
no I'm kind of like if it's like good
look like I did Lex Friedman because
like I had listened to Lex Friedman and
my rich well I was a lot more rich
before the coronavirus what is too much
coffee don't have more than 400
milligrams of caffeine today have you
ever spoken to Maddie you on yeah yeah
zinc and vitamin C you're these things
you hear a lot
Lex is getting good yeah what's my
investment advice I don't know man wait
for the markets to go back up
you take adderall not much anymore
almost never because leverage kudos
who's tensorflow man it's kind of
sausage picture PI torch where is Joe
Biden that's a great question no no how
much buy vitamin d3
[Music]
no no we're not now really we're not
really no no Joel I'm not well not the
poor guy man the poor guys might make
fun of Joe Biden you know what one of
the markets say I can't believe I I
can't believe I can't believe I know one
thinks he's gonna work I mean like maybe
you know Trump what's up do I think
Yvonne's attitude toward the virus is
good does he know that it's ours we
learned it's ours tonight what's C for
forever I don't know it's your favorite
news source I don't read the news it's
50/50 you know it's always 50/50 though
what should I do to go to space well you
know get a job at SpaceX being a janitor
and then before the rocket launches
climbing slide are you against video
games no I mean against can work at
rocket lab let's rock on top oh what's
the watch vehicle
electron rocket and these things have
made into orbit no all right so I'm not
that up today on space toys with this
it's the engine
Rutherford engines electric pump fad
wall walks rp1 terms of Falcone
whoa there's got to be a lot simpler
that's cool
I mean this is for turbo wow it looks so
simple
one for the fuel one for the oxidizer
generatively cooled
oh so this isn't to warm up the
propellant this is to cool the engine so
very cool
yeah cool Amazo why do you want to cool
the nozzle like what does it matter
you know it gets hot it'll melt can I
make it out of like tungsten or some
shit
let me can I have tungsten man what's it
George Hotz calm go I'm on that side
also my Chinese scam Wow
how about launching a payload I don't
know what do we want to send to space
how much
these people hiring this seems like a
sick place to work where they based
I don't know you lost me at like culture
engineering
how much is like a little satellite what
if I want to put a little satellite into
space you wish comma has a lame website
that talks about our shared values boo
cultural engineering socks what would I
use that satellite for I'm gonna spy on
the Russians what they do it Sputnik Wow
2200 per pound kill the sick the same
cost to sit let's put coronavirus in
space SpaceX will do small SATs - how do
they make sure my satellite doesn't mess
up everyone else's satellites SSL
sun-synchronous orbit
go to low-earth orbit 1 kilogram million
dollars and afford that Oh
it's a rideshare for space Wow a million
[Laughter]
detected for people to go to space at
least 75 kilograms watch this amazing
video what is it what is that it's a
scam they put an LED in there all right
guys
I'm gonna see how many subscribers we
got if we got a lot of subscribers we're
gonna stream again tomorrow if we didn't
get a lot of subscribers fuck them never
stream it again that's right
imagine eating a food
all right thank you thank you I'm glad
you're like that yeah you want to go get
some Coronas yeah have a good night
everybody